dazzlejunction.com 2019-04-15

# Dazzle Junction: Privacy Policy

Search Dazzle Junction   

**Personal Information:** You can access and browse this site without disclosing any personally identifiable information. We do not collect any personal information from you without voluntarily submission. An example of this would be if you were to send an email to us, you would voluntarily disclose your email address, so that we can reply. The address is not kept or shared, only used to reply to your inquiry. This site does not require registration. We will never ask for a password from you.

**Cookie and tracking technology** are used for gathering information to understand visitor usage. This includes aggregate data, such as, browser type, operating system, and the number of users visiting the site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Third Party Sites:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregate data such as your IP address, and clickstream information via cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. To opt-out of such information collection and use, please visit [NAI's opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). For further information, about the policies of the specific advertising companies used on this website, or to opt out of use of the DART cookie you may do so by visiting: [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In addition to advertisements, we also link to other sites that may be of interest to our visitors. Dazzle Junction is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked sites. We encourage you to read their privacy policy as well.

Aggregate Data may be shared with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or other investigation. This would only take place if we were permitted or required by law, trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud, or, investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

If you have any questions, please send an email to info(at)dazzlejunction.com. 

* * *
